PATRICIA PARKER

https://www.linkedin.com/in/patriciakayparker/ LinkedIn Profile https://github.com/pkpatricia GitHub Repo https://www.datacamp.com/profile/pkpatricia Data Camp Profile https://patriciaparker.co Personal Site

Skills Summary

Developer that is knowledgeable and experienced in Web Design, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Java, Spring Boot, Android, Ruby on Rails, Python and its SciPy libraries of NumPy, Pandas, and matplotlib, SQL, Excel, Tableau, Shopify, WordPress, Drupal, and the Adobe Creative Cloud of various software packages such as Illustrator and Photoshop.

Projects

To Do List Using the Java/Spring Boot Framework | https://finalproject-p.cfapps.io/ Faith Based E-Commerce Web Site Landing Page | https://patriciaparker.co/faith/

Experience

Trilogy Educational Services

Teaching Assistant and Tutor / Sept 2018 – July 2019

- Tracked Classroom attendance and learning progress.
- Graded Individual Homework Assignments and Group Projects.
- Provided tutoring and class room assistance to students utilizing SQL, JavaScript, Data Visualization, Python and its SciPy libraries of NumPy, Pandas, and Matplotlib.

Conjuncture Design

Web Developer Freelancer / April 2016 - present

- Design and Code Responsive E-Mails with testing done in Litmus.
- E-mail Marketing Campaigns created through MailChimp and/or Campaign Monitor.
- Create E-Commerce websites with CMS-Systems such as Shopify and WordPress.

Collabera

Data Entry Associate / Dec 2014 – July 2015

• Inputted and transposed technician repair notes form Diebold systems to Bank of America systems.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Lawrence Technological University in Southfield, MI